<INFOINT>
	<INTEREST>
		<NAME>Hacking</NAME>
		<TYPE>Technical</TYPE>
		<INFO>Hacking is an attempt to exploit a computer system or a private network inside a computer. Simply put, it is the unauthorised access to or control over computer network security systems for some illicit purpose.</INFO>
	</INTEREST>
	<INTEREST>
		<NAME>Dance</NAME>
		<TYPE>Miscellaneous</TYPE>
		<INFO>Dance is a performance art form consisting of purposefully selected sequences of human movement. This movement has aesthetic and symbolic value, and is acknowledged as dance by performers and observers within a particular culture.Dance can be categorized and described by its choreography, by its repertoire of movements, or by its historical period or place of origin.</INFO>
	</INTEREST>
	<INTEREST>
		<NAME>Basketball</NAME>
		<TYPE>Sports</TYPE>
		<INFO>Basketball is a sport that is played by two teams of five players on a rectangular court. The objective is to shoot a ball through a hoop 18 inches (46 cm) in diameter and mounted at a height of 10 feet (3.048 m) to backboards at each end of the court. The game was invented in 1891 by Dr. James Naismith, who would be the first basketball coach of the Kansas Jayhawks, one of the most successful programs in the game's history.</INFO>
	</INTEREST>
	<INTEREST>
		<NAME>Judo</NAME>
		<TYPE>Sports</TYPE>
		<INFO>Judo (柔道 jūdō?, meaning "gentle way") was created as a physical, mental and moral pedagogy in Japan, in 1882, by Jigoro Kano (嘉納治五郎). It is generally categorized as a modern martial art which later evolved into a combat and Olympic sport. Its most prominent feature is its competitive element, where the objective is to either throw or takedown an opponent to the ground, immobilize or otherwise subdue an opponent with a pin, or force an opponent to submit with a joint lock or a choke. Strikes and thrusts by hands and feet as well as weapons defenses are a part of judo, but only in pre-arranged forms (kata, 形) and are not allowed in judo competition or free practice (randori, 乱取り). A judo practitioner is called a judoka.</INFO>
	</INTEREST>
</INFOINT>